{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622576","name":"Ginger Berry LLC","address":"12626 E Jefferson Avenue","owner":"Alexis Posey","licenseNumber":"221928","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-82.95707,42.36988","geojson":{"id":"51622576","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.957072166,42.3698820990001]},"properties":{"name":"Ginger Berry LLC","owner":"Alexis Posey","address":"12626 E Jefferson Avenue","zipcode":"48215","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"221928","establishmentid":"51622576","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"9/20/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1391","name":"Joseph's Coney Island","address":"12500 E Jefferson Ave"},{"establishmentid":"5139","name":"Historic Eastlake Baptist Church","address":"12440 E Jefferson Ave"},{"establishmentid":"4440","name":"Jimmie's Lounge","address":"12625 Kercheval"},{"establishmentid":"4927","name":"Davis Aerospace Tech High @ Golightly Te","address":"900 Dickerson Ave"},{"establishmentid":"1388","name":"Golightly  Career Tech","address":"900 Dickerson Ave"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43144","inspectionDate":"2018-08-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Behind the Cookline","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41470","inspectionDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Bleach","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"violationCode":"6-501.113","violationDescription":"Maintenance tools such as brooms, mops, vacuum cleaners, and similar items shall be:\r\n(A) Stored so they do not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; and\r\n(B) Stored in an orderly manner that facilitates cleaning the area used for storing the maintenance tools.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Maintenance tool storage","subItem":"mops","problemDescription":"Unorganized","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in an orderly manner."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-201.14","violationDescription":"(A) Carpeting or similar material may not be installed as a floor covering in areas where the floor is subject to moisture, food spills, flushing, or spray cleaning methods. \r\n(B) If carpeting is installed as a floor covering in areas other than those specified above, it must be properly installed.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Carpet","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Carpeting","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Stove","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40545","inspectionDate":"2017-10-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"SERVICE WINDOW","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"for construction","problemDescription":"Not nonabsorbent in areas subject to moisture","subProblem":"Warewashing","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be non-absorbent."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"Floor is rough with peeling paint","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"WALL(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wood","subItem":"birch","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"WOOD","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"4-204.120","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT compartments that are subject to accumulation of moisture due to conditions such as condensation, FOOD or BEVERAGE drip, or water from melting ice shall be sloped to an outlet that allows complete draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment compartment(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sloped to drain","subProblem":"","location":"DISPLAY COUNTER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace so that sloped to drain."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622576"}}